[A Good Day to Ascend]
[Episode 2: The Deity Slayer, Xu Ying]
It looks like this kid can't continue
with this game anymore.
You've overestimated your own ability.
You don't seem as strong as I've imagined.
You had fun beating me up.
Now,
it's my turn.
You've practiced
cultivation techniques before?
You're kind of capable.
Since you're merely a mortal,
practicing cultivation techniques
is still useless.
How dare you compete with me in strength?
A strength technique, huh?
Shall I circulate the qi and blood
along this path?
Elephant Force Bull Fist!
The First Stance
of the Elephant Force Bull Fist—
Star-Piercing Strike!
The
second...
The third level!
The fourth level!
This strength...
How is this possible?
How dare you hurt my body?
I'll make sure
you'll die without a burial place!
The Second Stance
of the Elephant Force Bull Fist—
Double Happiness!
The Third Stance
of the Elephant Force Bull Fist—
Lucky Strike!
Wait!
I'm willing to
bring rain for the whole village!
I'm sorry.
I'll guarantee an abundant harvest
for the village!
♪ There are all kinds of ways ♪
♪ Saving people from impermanence ♪
How foolish!
How could I possibly
beg a nonentity for mercy?
♪ A mournful howl resounds ♪
It's time for your death, nonentity!
♪ Piercing the chest ♪
♪ Asking Heaven ♪
♪ What crimes
did the common people commit? ♪
You shouldn't have lied to me!
♪ Why should they be killed? ♪
This punch...
♪ Why? ♪
is to punish you
for forcing Uncle Jiang to his death!
This punch
is to punish you
for bullying Ms. Jiang Shu!
♪ The virtue of cherishing lives
is all in vain ♪
This punch
is to punish you
for not fulfilling your duty as a deity!
Please spare my life!
♪ Watching without doing anything ♪
♪ How ridiculous ♪
As for this punch,
it's just because I want to hit you!
♪ Who should we ask about karma? ♪
I'm registered both in the Phantom Capital
and the Imperial Court.
♪ Make conclusions ♪
If you kill me,
you'll violate the law of...
♪ Open your eyes and watch ♪
[Slaying the deity]
♪ When have we ever seen the shore
of suffering in the mortal world? ♪
I'm sorry, Ying! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Guys, you don't have to be afraid anymore.
I've killed the bad guy.
Why?
Monster!
God, please bless us.
What a sin, oh, what a sin.
I was standing up for you guys!
Don't look!
You shouldn't be afraid of me.
I did nothing wrong.
I killed a bad guy.
[The Deity Slayer, Xu Ying]
Thank you all
for taking care of me over these years.
I'm sorry for the trouble
I've caused you.
Ying!
Thank you.
You have to live on well.
Take care.
Xu Ying
reached the fifth level
of the Elephant Force Bull Fist
in just a short time?
I've practiced this fist technique
for decades, but...
Well, I have to ask him to teach me.
While Xu Ying was fleeing,
his act of killing a deity
caught the attention
of both the Lingling City God
[Phantom Realm, God of Land]
and the Zhou family, which was one
[Zhou Yang, Magistrate of Lingling]
of the Eight Great Nuo Shaman Families.
Father,
a case occurred in Jiang's Village.
A snake hunter named Xu Ying
killed both the councillor
and the Phantom Deity
that was worshipped by Jiang's Village.
He's currently on the run.
Since he was able
to kill the Phantom Deity,
[Zhou Yihang, Governor of Lingling]
is this snake hunter a Nuo Shaman?
This is what I'd like to tell you, Father.
These were found in Xu Ying's house.
The demon race's cultivation techniques
at the qi gathering stage.
So Xu Ying practiced
the demon race's cultivation techniques?
[Xue Lingfu, Lingling City God]
My Lord,
look at the annotations at the back.
Xu Ying's annotations
are absolute nonsense.
What an idiot.
[Ximen Grimoire]
This person's understanding
of demonic techniques
is extremely profound now.
Even the elders of my Zhou family
who study this might not surpass him.
These demonic techniques
are just some fragments
of mantras at the qi gathering stage.
Why would...
The matter
of the demon race's cultivation techniques
has a wide and significant impact.
Pass on my order.
All Phantom Deities,
officers
and Nuo Shamans around Lingling
should spare no effort to capture Xu Ying.
Don't kill him.
I want him alive.
Yes, sir!
Also,
if the Nuo Shamans of the Zhou family
find Xu Ying first,
then just kill him without hesitation.
We must make sure that
even if Xu Ying
is dead,
- his body can't be taken by the Phantom Capital.
- his body can't be taken by the Zhou family.
[The next day]
Guys, guard every intersection.
[Feng Yi, Phantom Deity
of Huangni Bridge Village]
Don't slack off.
That guy named Xu Ying
will definitely pass through this place.
We can't let him get away.
Oh, no.
There are people everywhere!
Just see what I'll do.
There is a snake demon!
My Lady, save me!
Where did this little demon come from?
I'll just kill you!
Her Ladyship is mighty!
With the coming storm on the mountain,
the wind...
Only a fool would wait for your nagging.
Her Ladyship got eaten!
[Again, the next day]
[Five Herbs Man,
Phantom Deity of Tugang Village]
Xu Ying, you bold thief!
Under the order of the City God...
Step aside!
[Yuan Ling,
Phantom Deity of Zao's Village]
You're just in time, Xu Ying!
Kneel down!
Get lost!
[Huan Ledou, Phantom Deity of Gouzitou]
[Nian Xiu, River God of Sanlidu]
Yuanqi!
Do it now!
May you be prosperous!
[Jiu Wangcai,
Phantom Deity of Bai's Village]
May you be prosperous!
Brat, stop right there!
[Mang Hao,
Mountain God of Mount Hong]
You can't catch up with me, huh?
Run faster!
This guy can't run fast.
We can just make him run to death.
Shut up!
If you keep nagging,
I'll throw you down as bait.
Stop!
Come out at once!
The God of Mount Hong
is really a nuisance.
Fortunately, he is too slow.
Otherwise, we would really be in trouble.
Well, Yuan...
Just call me Niu.
My ancestor
practiced the Elephant Force Bull Fist.
Therefore, he took the surname Niu.
When I was born, my father said
our kind of venomous snake
was called Yuan in ancient times.
I am the seventh child,
so he named me Yuanqi.
Niu.
It refers to Bull
in the Elephant Force Bull Fist.
But it doesn't mean turning yourself
into a bull demon through the cultivation.
Rather, it means
when practicing this fist technique,
you should be as fearless as a bull demon.
This fist technique
has nothing to do with bulls.
So you mean
my ancestor misunderstood
the Elephant Force Bull Fist?
My name is correct.
But my family's surname is wrong.
How about
you change your surname?
My ancestor's surname was Niu.
My father's surname was Niu.
How could I forget my roots
and betray my ancestors?
A true man never changes his name.
My name is Yuanqi!
Now you're not mentioning your surname.
Why did you call my name just now?
You said we could go to Mount Wuwang
to take refuge.
Where is it?
My Qinyan Cave is on Mount Wuwang.
It's an ancient relic,
which is actually a good place to hide.
However, we need to walk 200 miles.
200 miles?
Including the Mountain God
who chased us just now,
there have been 10 deities already, right?
We left Jiang's Village
and headed for Mount Wuwang.
We haven't even gone a few dozen miles,
but we've encountered
so many Phantom Deities trying to stop us.
It looks like the City God
has issued an order to kill you.
In Lingling, with its 800 mountains
and 500 rivers,
plus its lakes and villages,
there are at least over 2,000
Phantom Deities.
We've been walking along
the most desolate paths as much as possible.
These Phantom Deities
on the wild mountains
were designated as deities
by the demon race.
They're more powerful than the ones
worshipped in towns and villages.
The City God's kill order
is targeted at me.
If we really can't escape from here,
you can just leave by yourself.
I... I can leave by myself?
What about you?
A true man bears the consequences
of his own actions.
I killed the Phantom Deity.
I'll bear
all the consequences by myself.
It's good to say, "A true man
bears the consequences
of his own actions."
The cries of nonentities
are truly pleasant to hear.
Government official?
Oh, no.
Xu Ying.
Lingling City
is the Zhou family's territory.
You killed Councillor Jiang
and broke the Zhou family's rules.
Just surrender and face your punishment.
[Ding Quan, Judicial Officer of Lingling]
He colluded with the Phantom Deity
and disregarded human lives,
so he deserved to die.
Human lives?
The lives of you nonentities
are nothing
compared to Magistrate Zhou's prestige.
My name's Ding Quan.
I'm a judicial officer in Lingling.
You're a Nuo Shaman?
Yes.
I am a Nuo Shaman.
This is the orthodox cultivation method
of our human race.
It's to discover the secrets
of human bodies
and succeed in the method
of becoming an immortal.
It's totally different
from the demonic techniques
you've been practicing randomly.
I've heard that Nuo techniques
are only spread among some noble families.
Your deceased parents were useless.
Their son is also a loser.
You deserve to be trampled on.
My Nuo techniques
come precisely
from the great Zhou family of Yongzhou.
If you work as hard as I did,
you can also
gain the Zhou family's appreciation.
So you mean being a lackey
for the Zhou family?
And you actually feel superior about it?
You don't even have the chance
to be a lackey!
Today, you'll see
[In the next episode]
the orthodox Nuo arts you've never seen
in your life.
Congratulations, Lord Stone Mountain God.
The credit for capturing Xu Ying
will surely be yours.
Come on.
Let's go take a look.
There are so many ghosts
coming out of the realm.
I'm afraid
the mortal world will be in trouble.